medic8.com 2007-07-09

# The Medic8 Family Health Guide: Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Medic8 does not rent, sell, or trade customer details with anyone. All customer information is held in strict confidence. Any information collected is for the sole purpose of providing services described on this web site.

**Personal Information**

This site collects personally identifiable information.

Personal information such as name, email, postal address, etc are collected for the sole purpose of providing services described on this web site. Such personally-identifiable information will only be collected if you voluntarily choose to disclose such information. 

The information you provide to us will be stored on computer. We may use the information you provide to provide a more personalised service and to tell you about changes in our service or any new services which we think you will find valuable. You may unsubscribe from any such notifications at any time.

All customer information is held in strict confidence.

**Cookies**

Cookies are bits of electronic information that a website can transfer to your hard drive to help tailor and keep records of your visit to this site. Cookies help us to provide you with the best possible service on our site. We use cookies to see where visitors are coming from and tracking user interests and behaviour. 

If you voluntarily provide personal details, we may use cookies to identify what pages and topics are of specific interest to you. Most major websites use cookies and their use is standard on the internet. Most internet browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can change your settings so that you are notified whenever you are sent a cookie, or block them completely should you wish to do this.

We also use cookies for remembering items that you may add to your shopping basket when browsing our health store. When you close your browser, these cookies are deleted automatically.

To learn more about cookies, [click here](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

**Hyperlinks**

Our website may contain links to other websites. Other websites may also reference or link to our website(s). We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites and expressly disclaim all liability associated with your use of and the content on such other websites. 

**General**

We may change our privacy policy in the future. Any changes to our privacy policy will be made available online at www.medic8.com/healthguide/privacy.htm \- a "last revised" date will always be included on the bottom of the statement. 

Last revised: 15th November 2005
